<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="146816" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Elections [RT Module]" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Adds mayoral election campaigns where the winning candidate shapes the city's next year, while the player can influence the race to help their preferred candidate win." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
Elections adds a mayoral election cycle to the city. Residents can become candidates, campaigns can release polls, voters travel to polling places on election day, and the winning mayor applies a platform effect until the next election.

## Dependencies and Compatibility

**Important:** Elections requires Realistic Trips. Realistic Trips has a large impact on gameplay, so if you are not familiar with it, please take a look at Realistic Trips first before using this mod. Realistic Trips owns the calendar, time behavior, voting trips, mayor policy hooks, and special election-day travel requests used by this mod. Custom Chirps is used for election announcements, candidate messages and mayor messages.

## What This Mod Adds

* **Mayoral Campaigns:** Eligible residents are selected as candidates, receive generated profiles and platforms, and campaign before election day.
* **Campaign:** Use campaign actions such as donations, civic programs, mayor outreach, endorsements, and vote-tampering attempts.
* **Voting Trips:** On election day, residents can travel to polling places through Realistic Trips. Results are announced after voting closes.
* **Mayor Effects:** The elected mayor applies a city policy effect until the next term. Platforms can include positive benefits and tradeoffs.
* **Civic Programs:** The city can fund limited campaign-season programs such as turnout education, an election-day holiday, or strict voting ID proposals.
* **Campaign Donations and Meetings:** The city can fund campaign donations, mayor outreach meetings, endorsements, and other campaign actions.
* **Election Events:** Campaigns can trigger chirps, candidate statements, corruption investigations, vote-tampering incidents, victory messages, and mayor transition messages.

## Settings

* **General:** Enable or disable elections and choose whether the Elections button appears in Universal Mod Menu.
* **Voting:** Configure poll sample size, voting hours, and age-turnout values or country presets.
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshot1.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshot2.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshot3.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshot4.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshot5.jpg" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/elections-mod.1927087/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.3" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.5.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="77171" />
	<Dependency Id="121812" />
	<!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times. Supported values are "Landmark Buildings", "San Fransisco Set", "Beach Properties", "Urban Promenades", "Modern Architecture"-->
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>
* Added configurable two to four candidate races and optional runoff elections.
* Added optional political parties with editable names and colors, persistent reputation, win and term tracking, party tags, and party effects on voting behavior.
* Added candidate traits that can affect voter support, donation costs, turnout, campaign effectiveness, mayor actions, and platform effects.
* Added election legislation and expanded civic programs.
* Expanded campaign actions with daily donation limits, mayor endorsements and bribe meetings, cash assistance, vote-count tampering, and improved corruption/scandal handling.
* Reworked polling and results for multi-candidate races with larger poll samples, undecided handling, margin-of-error summaries, and age, education, and income breakdowns.
* Rebuilt the Elections panel with clearer sections for schedule, voting sites, mayor residence/workplace, candidates, programs, legislation, parties, and richer tooltips/status messaging.
* Improved voting-site overlays and election-day voting behavior with multi-candidate vote rings, party/candidate colors, election-day holiday scheduling, and better vote-trip timing.
* Added more candidate portraits.
	</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/ruzbeh0/Elections" />
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.com/channels/1024242828114673724/1513124497300127764" />
	<ExternalLink Type="youtube" Url="https://youtu.be/fVCW2Lly_Cw" />
	<ExternalLink Type="paypal" Url="https://www.paypal.com/paypalme/ruzbeh0" />
	<ExternalLink Type="kofi" Url="https://ko-fi.com/ruzbeh0" />
	<!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
